Alright, we are ready to talk about solutions.
And at this point in the program, what you want to do is pose possible solutions.
Now you notice I stressed possible, because, you're going to come up with some solutions, but, it, don't think in terms of well these are our solutions, and if these don't work, then the relationship is over.
You may go through a number of solutions, before you find what actually works, to repair the relationship.
The first thing, we have to look at when posing a solution, is think in terms of win-win strategies.
You don't want a win-lose strategy, that will not repair the relationship.
And what I'm talking about win-lose versus win-win.
I get everything I want, you get nothing.
OK, this is what I want, this is the relationship that I see and I'm going to get all of it.
The other person loses.
So, win-win starts to become about compromise.
These are the things that I really really want.
This is what you really really want, so I'm going to have to compromise a little, you're going to have to compromise a little, so that we can both win.
And that's what you're going for as you start to pose and create these solutions.